a terrible problem that afflicts many of us is
困扰我们许多人的一个可怕问题是
that we are almost permanently anxious
我们几乎永远都很焦虑
self critical
自我批评
self hating
自我憎恨
and afflicted by a sense that we don't deserve to exist
被一种我们不配存在的感觉所折磨
we are definitely not good enough ever
我们绝对不够好
psychology points us to a part of
心理学给我们指出了
the mind termed our conscience
思想称我们的良知
a faculty that keeps an eye on how well
一个密切关注有多好的教师
we're doing in relation to duty
我们正在做的与职责有关的事情
to the demands of the world
满足世界的要求
and to the regulation of our desires and appetites
以及调节我们的欲望和食欲
our conscience monitors how much effort we're putting into
我们的良心会监督我们付出了多少努力
our work and our ratio of relaxed rest to anxious labor
我们的工作和放松休息与焦虑劳动的比率
it's our conscience that tells us when
是我们的良心告诉我们什么时候
we've probably done enough gaming
我们可能玩够了
dating or eating
约会还是吃饭
however useful this function may sound
无论这个功能听起来多么有用
for many of us our conscience has grown very unbalanced
对我们中的许多人来说，我们的良心变得非常不平衡
rather than occasionally gently nudging us towards virtue
而不是偶尔温柔地推动我们走向美德
it is permanently screaming
它永远在尖叫
denigrating and attacking us for perceived failings
诋毁和攻击我们的缺点
it tells us that nothing we do is ever good enough
它告诉我们我们做的任何事都不够好
that we have no right to take a holiday
我们没有权利去度假
let alone an afternoon off
更别说休息一下午了
that we have no business relaxing or enjoying ourselves
我们没有理由放松或享受
and that the worst is coming to us
最坏的情况正在向我们袭来
because of our sinful nature
因为我们罪恶的本性
anxiety and self - contempt are our default states
焦虑和自卑是我们的默认状态
it was freud's simple but brilliant insight
这是弗洛伊德简单而卓越的见解
that our conscience is formed out of the
我们的良心是由
residue of the voices of our parents
父母声音的残余
in particular usually of our fathers
尤其是我们的父亲
freud called the conscience the super ego and
弗洛伊德称良心为超级自我意识
proposed that this faculty continues to speak within
提议该系继续在内部发言
our minds as our father figures once spoke to us
我们的思想就像我们的父亲曾经告诉我们的那样
for the lucky ones among us
为了我们中的幸运儿
we had reasonable father figures
我们有合理的父亲形象
and therefore our consciences are broadly benign
因此我们的良心基本上是良性的
if we fail today
如果我们今天失败了
we can try again next time
我们下次可以再试一次
if we're unpopular
如果我们不受欢迎
we can be valuable anyway
反正我们也能有价值
we deserve a rest
我们应该休息一下
sex is allowed
性是允许的
treats are a part of life
款待是生活的一部分
we can do nothing for a while
我们暂时无能为力
we're OK as we are
我们现在很好
but for others among us
但对我们中的其他人来说
our conscience rehearses the worst
我们的良心预演最坏的情况
lines of punitive parental archetypes
惩罚性父母原型
when things go wrong
当事情出错时
we swiftly conclude that it might be
我们很快得出结论可能是
better if we killed ourselves
我们还是自杀比较好
one of the steps we can take towards greater
我们可以采取的步骤之一
mental health is to realize properly realize
心理健康是正确认识到
that this drama is going on inside us
这场戏剧正在我们内心上演
it sounds strange to say given the significance
这么说听起来很奇怪
but usually we have no clue
但通常我们毫无头绪
the self criticism has become too
自我批评也变得
familiar to be noticeable
熟悉而引人注目
it's just how things are and who we are
事情就是这样，我们是谁
we can't draw a distinction between the
我们不能区分
fierce inner critic and any other part of us
激烈的内心批评和我们的任何其他部分
a crucial first move is therefore to learn to put some
因此，关键的第一步是学会把一些
distance between ourselves and our conscience
我们与良心之间的距离
we should see our conscience as a character
我们应该把我们的良心看作是一个角色
we should tell ourselves
我们应该告诉自己
i have a punishing inner critic
我有一个惩罚性的内心批评
and it's very unfair to me
这对我很不公平
it's even sometimes trying to kill me
它有时甚至想杀了我
it's speaking to me within me
它在我体内对我说话
but it isn't all i am
但这不是我的全部
it's someone i sucked in from childhood
是我从小就被吸进去的人
and might learn to expel from my mind in time
也许会及时学会从我的脑海中驱逐
we can then start to question the critic
然后我们可以开始质疑批评家
is it really fair to say that our
说我们的
lives are wholly worthless
生命毫无价值
we've messed up for sure
我们肯定搞砸了
but do we really deserve no compassion and no forgiveness
但是我们真的不值得同情和原谅吗？
is nothing about us in any way good
我们之间没有什么好的
would we ever think of treating a friend or even
我们会考虑治疗朋友甚至
an enemy the way we're treating ourselves
我们对待自己的方式就是敌人
we had no choice about who we had to
我们没有选择我们必须找谁
listen to when we were little
听着我们小时候
but we do now have agency
但我们现在确实有代理
we can retrain our minds by getting better at spotting
我们可以通过更好地观察来重新训练我们的大脑
how they were indoctrinated in the first place
他们最初是如何被灌输的
we have picked up some extremely
我们发现了一些非常
cruel and questionable habits
恶习
no one needs to be hounded by a
没有人需要被一个
sense that they are excrement
感觉它们是粪便
this feeling has a past
这种感觉有过去
and it doesn't have to be the future
也不一定是未来
to retrain ourselves
重新训练自己
we need other people
我们需要其他人
people who can love us and fill our
可以爱我们并充满我们的人
minds with other kinder perspectives
具有其他更善良视角的思想
we need to dare to lean on them
我们要敢于依靠他们
not an easy move for people who feel
对于那些觉得
undeserving in the first place
一开始就不配
and ask for their help in taming
并请求他们帮助驯服
the nasty soundtrack inside
里面讨厌的配乐
we should stop trying to be brave
我们应该停止勇敢
about the inner attacks we host
关于我们主持的内心攻击
we might explicitly say to others
我们可能会明确地对别人说
you're here to help me with my inner critic
你是来帮我解决我内心的批判的
and to give me new perspectives on
并给我新的视角
my self punishment and despair
我的自我惩罚和绝望
we should at times get incensed that we
我们有时应该生气，因为我们
have to live with such a critic
不得不和这样的批评家生活在一起
and question why our first impulse is
并质疑为什么我们的第一个冲动是
so often to forgive the critic
经常原谅批评家
and the parental figure who inspired it
以及启发它的父母形象
and blame ourselves for our stupidity
为自己的愚蠢而自责
we need to feel sorry for ourselves and annoyed with
我们需要为自己感到难过和恼火
those who didn't know how to show us tenderness  of course
那些不懂温柔的人
we occasionally need to upbraid ourselves and try harder
我们偶尔需要责备自己，更加努力
but the real achievement is to know how to
但真正的成就是知道如何
remain gently and generously on our own side
温柔大方地站在我们这边
self knowledge is a new essay book that
自我认识是一本新的作文书
takes us on a journey into our deepest
带我们进入我们最深处的旅程
most elusive selves
最难以捉摸的自我
and arms us with a set of tools to
用一套工具武装我们
understand our characters properly
正确理解我们的角色